

Ben Logan

BUSINESS PARTNER

ABOUT

I am a person who values team work and building strong relationships with internal and external stakeholders. My previous experience in accounting and finance has helped to hone those skills, as well as develop the critical thinking and problem solving skills necessary for a successful career in UX Design. Combine that with my passion for creative art and design, I believe I will make a strong contribution in the field of UX Design.

CONTACT

+21 120 2326

benjaminlogan22@gmail.com

Auckland, New Zealand

SKILLS

Team Player

Time Management Communication **Problem Solving** Presentation

ဓ

WORK EXPERIENCE

Beca Group

Business Partner - Innovation Revenue 2021 - Present

This role is dedicated to sourcing opportunities across the business to qualify projects that meet the criteria for the R&D Tax Incentive.

- Strong communication skills engaging with industry leaders across the business
- · Presentations generating buy-in from wider business to build engagement and maximise R&D benefit
- · Facilitation of training sessions and workshops
- · Listen, understand and assess information against criteria

Bellingham Wallace

Senior Accountant 2020 - 2021

Providing business advisory services to a broad range of clients from different industries to solve complex business problems and accountancy services

- Management of client portfolio
- · Build strong relationships with internal and external stakeholders
- · Ensure timeliness, accuracy and usefulness of financial management reporting

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

Certificate UX Design

Dec 2022 - Present

• Part-time course applying fundamentals of design thinking to business case scenarios

Chartered Accountants ANZ

2016 - 2019

University of Auckland

Bachelor of Commerce

2011 - 2015

· Accounting and Commercial Law